### Dr JAMIL ANWER

Hospital Pharmacist at Mardan

jamilkakakheil@gmail.com

00923451198006

## Summary

Graduate in pharmacy from university of Malakand in 2012 and joined Rehman Medical institute Peshawar for a period of six months as a trainee pharmacist but side by side i worked as a hospital pharmacist for New AlShifa hospital mardan. After successful completion of training at RMI, i came to shifa and working there till now.

## Experience

### Hospital Pharmacist at New Alshifa Medical Center Mardan

August 2013 - April 2016 (2 years 9 months)

Hospital Pharmacist

### hospital pharmacist at Rehman Medical Institute (RMI)

December 2012 - June 2013 (7 months)

Patient counselling, medication error repoting, prescriptions handling and evaluation, ward rounds, floor stock checking, oncological drugs monitoring, developing patient safety methods

## Skills & Expertise

**Hospital Pharmacy** 

**Team Leadership** 

**Teamwork** 

**Time Management** 

**Collaborative Problem Solving** 

**Corporate Communications** 

**Institutional Sales** 

**Pharmacy** 

Medicine

**Patient Counselling** 

**Patient Safety** 

## Education

### University of Malakand

Doctor of Pharmacy (Pharm.D), Pharmacy, 2007 - 2012

Grade: B+

Activities and Societies: blood donor society and hiking club

### **Government Post Graduate College Mardan**

HSSC, PREMEDICAL (Science group), 2005 - 2007

Grade: A

Activities and Societies: social activist and Debater

## Hira High School Takht Bhai

SSC, Science group, 2002 - 2004

Grade: A

Activities and Societies: Debater and social awareness society member

#### Interests

Main area of interest is to develop pharmacy professionalism in Pakistan.

## Languages

English (Professional working proficiency)

**Urdu** (Full professional proficiency)

## Volunteer Experience

# Making Interventions and corrections in Patients medication Charts at Saidu Group of Teaching hospitals Swat

January 2012 - Present

Volunteer working in first round started from January 2012 to June 2012

# interventions and correction in Medication Errors in Patient Medication charts at Saidu Group of Teaching Hospitals Swat

July 2012 - Present

july to december 2012 was a next round to do volunteer working

### Certifications

### National Symposium on Old plants new remedies

University of Malakand, Pakistan

### Honors and Awards

### Got first position in SSC board exam in

**Tehsil** hira high school takht bhai

September 2004

#### First position holder in HSSC in college

Received award from principal of the college

2005

## **Projects**

### Pharmacotherapy of congestive heart failure

November 2012 to Present

Members: Dr JAMIL ANWER

## Organizations

## **Rehman Medical Institute**

Worked as a Team leader in training period.

December 2012 to June 2013

## **Dr JAMIL ANWER**

Hospital Pharmacist at Mardan

jamilkakakheil@gmail.com